footprint360.com 2016-10-22

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy - Our Commitment**

We respect and value your trust in us and your privacy is very important to us. We do not publish, sell or share your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.

**Policy Updates**

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this Website

**Terms and Conditions**

By using this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If at any time you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website and refrain from purchasing from us online. By mere use of the Website you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By accessing the services provided by us and/or your placing an order on the Website you agree to the collection and use of your data by us in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy.

**User/Buyer Information Collected**

**Collection of Information:**

You can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Wherever possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You may have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address etc.

You can delete your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our Website. We will collect personally identifiable information about you only as part of a voluntary registration process, on-line survey, or contest or any combination thereof.

**Use of Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. We use data collection devices such as cookies on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties

**Use of the Information Collected**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information for marketing and advertisement to you, We will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyse site usage, improve the Website's content and product offerings, and customize the Website's content, layout, and services. You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you. We use your personal information to:

  * resolve disputes
  * troubleshoot problems
  * help promote a safe service
  * collect money
  * measure consumer interest in our products and services,
  * inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates;
  * customize your experience
  * detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity
  * enforce our terms and conditions and
  * as otherwise described to you at the time of collection
  * communicate you about our product offerings

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyse demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website. We may identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.

**Information we Share**

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our customers, except as described herein. We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, detect correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services, and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy, respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party, or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users. We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**User’s Choice with Respect to the Information Collected**

We provide all Users/Buyers with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional, marketing-related communications from us after setting up an account. You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time. We reserve our right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your account without offering you the facility to opt-out.  Upon request, we will remove/block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby cancelling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.

**Grievance Officer**

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

Mr [?]   
Reliance Footprint  
No 62/2, First Floor, Reliance Retail, Richmond Road, Bangalore - 560025  
Phone:   
Email: -

**Security of Information Collected**

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. Our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel on need to know basis to complete the transaction and to provide the services requested by you. Although we will endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet or telecom or other network/s cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Website you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable security practices and procedures and current internet security methods and technologies in compliance with Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under.

**Miscellaneous**

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Website links to other Websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked Websites

**Advertisements**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this Website and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you

**Children's Privacy**

Children are not eligible to use our Website and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) to not to submit any personal information to us. If you wish to purchase an item on the Website such purchase may be made by your legal guardian or parents who are users of the Website provided that such purchase or sale is not in relation to any adult material/mature audience items displayed on the Website, the sale of which to minors is strictly prohibited.
